Guide to the Dennis Cooper Papers ca. 1970-2002 MSS 085
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Book projects and correspondence of writers and artists
  - Ray, Charles, undated (Box 8, Folder 442c)
  - Ray, Charles., undated (Box 8, Folder 442)
  - Rene Ricard, correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 443)
  - Sheree Rose, photos., undated (Box 8, Folder 444)
  - David Salle, correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 445)
  - Jon Savage, articles by Savage, undated (Box 8, Folder 446)
  - Jon Savage, correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 447)
  - Peter Schjeldahl, The Friendless Bodies. manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 448)
  - Peter Schjeldahl, "How to Be Alive" manuscript and photograph, undated (Box 8, Folder 449)
  - Peter Schjeldahl, interview by Cooper, undated (Box 8, Folder 450)
  - Peter Schjeldahl, correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 451)
  - David Sedaris, "Caesura" manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 452)
  - David Sedaris, "The Snatches" manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 453)
  - David Sedaris, correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 454)
  - Ira Silverberg, correspondence and promotional material, undated (Box 8, Folder 455)
  - Michael Silverblatt, manuscript, undated (Box 16, Folder 455a)
  - Jack Skelley, "Aliens Don't Need Doctors" manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 456)
  - Jack Skelley, "Artificial Heart" manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 457)
  - Jack Skelley, "Disco Paradiso" manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 458)
  - Jack Skelley, "Making Pigeons Pay" manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 459)
  - Jack Skelley, "Manhunt in Kowloon" manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 460)
  - Jack Skelley, poems, undated (Box 8, Folder 461)
  - Jack Skelley, "Public Image at the Olympic" manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 462)
  - Jack Skelley, "Smogman Laments His Task" manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 463)
  - Jack Skelley, "Wammo Amnesia" manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 464)
  - Jack Skelley, correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 465)
  - Jack Skelley, reviews., undated (Box 8, Folder 466)
  - Jack Skelley, Barney magazine promotional material, undated (Box 8, Folder 467)
  - Jack Skelley, Planet of Toys promotional material, undated (Box 8, Folder 468)
  - Jack Skelley, promotional material and photos, undated (Box 8, Folder 469)
  - Matthew Stadler, The Sex Offender manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 470)
  - Matthew Stadler, The Sex Offender manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 470a)
  - Matthew Stadler, untitled manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 471)
  - Matthew Stadler, correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 472)
  - Matthew Stadler, correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 471a)
  - Frances Stark, "She was a Type," et, undated (Box 8, Folder 473)
  - Frances Stark, untitled manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 474)
  - Frances Stark, "Upon My Arrival", undated (Box 8, Folder 475)
  - Frances Stark, correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 476)
  - Mark Sullivan, Essay on Cooper's poetry/correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 476aa)
  - Terminator, untitled manuscripts, undated (Box 16, Folder 476a)
  - Terminator, untitled manuscripts, undated (Box 16, Folder 476b)
  - Terminator, correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 476c)
  - Lynne Tillman, "A Dead Summer" manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 477)
  - Lynne Tillman, untitled manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 478)
  - Lynne Tillman, correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 479)
  - David Trinidad, Answer Song manuscript, undated (Box 16, Folder 479a)
  - David Trinidad, Pavane manuscript, undated (Box 16, Folder 479b)
  - David Trinidad, "Secret Agent Girl", undated (Box 16, Folder 479c)
  - David Trinidad, various poems, undated (Box 16, Folder 479)
  - David Trinidad, correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 479e)
  - David Trinidad, reviews and promotional material, undated (Box 16, Folder 479)
  - Bruce Wagner, Wild Palms manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 480)
  - David Foster Wallace, correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 481)
  - John Waters, correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 482)
  - John Waters, correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 482a)
  - John Waters, interview, undated (Box 8, Folder 483)
  - Benjamin Weissman, "Assignment: Outback" manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 484)
  - Benjamin Weissman, "Battle " manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 485)
  - Benjamin Weissman, "The Confident Mother" manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 486)
  - Benjamin Weissman, "Dark Marks" manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 487)
  - Benjamin Weissman, "Flesh for Hacking" manuscript, undated (Box 8, Folder 488)
  - Benjamin Weissman, Interview of Cooper, undated (Box 8, Folder 488a)
  - Benjamin Weissman, "On My Birthday" manuscript, undated (Box 9, Folder 489)
  - Benjamin Weissman, "Our Lizards" manuscript, undated (Box 9, Folder 490)
  - Benjamin Weissman, untitled manuscript, undated (Box 9, Folder 491)
  - Benjamin Weissman, correspondence, undated (Box 9, Folder 492)
  - Bernard Welt, review of Gooch and Cooper, undated (Box 9, Folder 492a)
  - Edmund White, manuscript on Cooper, undated (Box 9, Folder 493)
  - David Wojnarowicz, Close to the Knives manuscript, undated (Box 9, Folder 494)
  - David Wojnarowicz, correspondence, undated (Box 9, Folder 495)
  - Ian Young, correspondence, undated (Box 9, Folder 496)
  - Ian Young, promotional material, undated (Box 9, Folder 497)
- Series III: Journalism
  Scope and Contents note
  [Includes Tearsheets of articles]
  - Subseries A: The Advocate
    - "Great Expectations", undated (Box 9, Folder 498)
    - "Home Entertainment column", undated (Box 9, Folder 499)
    - article on porn, undated (Box 9, Folder 500)
    - review "Trading Secrets", undated (Box 9, Folder 501)
    - "The East Village and its Gay Ways", undated (Box 9, Folder 502)
    - review of The Hustler, undated (Box 9, Folder 503)
    - "Letter from Amsterdam", undated (Box 9, Folder 504)
    - "Schuyler's A Few Days ", undated (Box 9, Folder 505)
    - "Tom of Finland", undated (Box 9, Folder 506)
    - Cooper's "Private Hit List", undated (Box 9, Folder 507)
  - Subseries B: Artforum - Los Angeles Times
    - Gregg Araki piece, undated (Box 9, Folder 508)
    - Book selection, undated (Box 9, Folder 509)
    - "Chris Burden", undated (Box 9, Folder 510)
    - "George Condo", undated (Box 9, Folder 511)
    - "End of the Year", undated (Box 9, Folder 512)
    - "Kate Ericson", undated (Box 9, Folder 513)
    - "Vincent Fecteau", undated (Box 9, Folder 514)
    - "Fictions", undated (Box 9, Folder 515)
    - "Bob Flanagan", undated (Box 9, Folder 516)
    - Joni Lee Mabe, undated (Box 9, Folder 517)
    - Review of McDermott and McGough, undated (Box 9, Folder 518)
    - Review of Cookie Mueller, undated (Box 9, Folder 519)
    - "Openings", undated (Box 9, Folder 520)
    - "Openings: Richard", undated (Box 9, Folder 521)
    - Review of Larry Clar's "The Perfect Childhood", undated (Box 9, Folder 522)
    - "Lari Pittman", undated (Box 9, Folder 523)
    - "Placebomania ", undated (Box 9, Folder 524)
    - "Pulp the Hype", undated (Box 9, Folder 524a.)
    - "Real Life Rock", undated (Box 9, Folder 525)
    - Review of Wallace and Donohue, undated (Box 9, Folder 526)
    - Review of Wojnarowicz, undated (Box 9, Folder 527)
    - Review of "Jim Isermann", undated (Box 9, Folder 528)
    - Art in America, "Report from Amsterdam", undated (Box 9, Folder 529)
    - Art Issues, "Letter from New York", undated (Box 9, Folder 530)
    - Artpaper, "On Pro Wrestling", undated (Box 9, Folder 531)
    - Art Press, "Poems", undated (Box 9, Folder 532)
    - Artscribe, "Shotgun: William Burroughs", undated (Box 9, Folder 533)
    - Attitude, Q&A, undated (Box 9, Folder 534)
    - Bay Windows, review of Lasting Relations, undated (Box 9, Folder 535)
    - Cups, Interview of Cooper, undated (Box 9, Folder 536)
    - Detour, "Christian Bale", undated (Box 9, Folder 536a.)
    - Detour, "Rebel Just Because", undated (Box 9, Folder 537)
    - A Different Corner, "Tomorrow Never Knows", undated (Box 9, Folder 538)
    - George, "Sonny Bono", undated (Box 9, Folder 539)
    - George, correspondence, undated (Box 9, Folder 540)
    - GOSH!, "The L.A. Book Fair", undated (Box 9, Folder 541)
    - Grand Street, Interview with Charles Ray, undated (Box 9, Folder 542)
    - ID Magazine, correspondence, undated (Box 9, Folder 543)
    - In Style, "Four Marines", undated (Box 9, Folder 544)
    - In Touch for Men, "Celebrity Christmas Lists", undated (Box 9, Folder 545)
    - L.A. Times survey, undated (Box 9, Folder 546)
  - Subseries C: L.A. Weekly
    - Article on Isermann, undated (Box 9, Folder 547)
    - "High on Context", undated (Box 9, Folder 548)
    - Review of Matthew Stadler, undated (Box 9, Folder 549)
    - Article on Derek Jarman, undated (Box 9, Folder 550)
    - On Dennis Cooper by Eric Latzky, undated (Box 9, Folder 551)
    - "Delirium Temblors", undated (Box 9, Folder 552)
    - "Fassbinder", undated (Box 9, Folder 553)
    - Review of Gary Indiana, undated (Box 9, Folder 554)
    - "Jim Isermann's Neo-Optimism", undated (Box 9, Folder 555)
    - "Inserts by Mark Ewert and Amy Gerstler", undated (Box 9, Folder 556)
    - "Inside the High", undated (Box 9, Folder 556a)
    - Review of Philadelphia, undated (Box 9, Folder 557)
    - "The Necessity of the Small Press", undated (Box 9, Folder 558)
    - "How Gordon Lish Became >Gordon Lish", undated (Box 9, Folder 558a)
    - "Point of Disorder", undated (Box 9, Folder 559)
    - "Sonic Youth", undated (Box 9, Folder 560)
    - Review of Brodky's Profane, undated (Box 9, Folder 561)
    - "Reservoir Dogs", undated (Box 9, Folder 562)
    - Matador Article on Pavement, undated (Box 9, Folder 563)
  - Subseries D: New York Native
    - "Love's Glare", undated (Box 9, Folder 564)
    - "Polymorphously Perverse", undated (Box 9, Folder 565)
    - "Teen Idols", undated (Box 9, Folder 566)
    - "Transcendent Trivia", undated (Box 9, Folder 567)
    - Summer Vacation Survey, undated (Box 9, Folder 568)
    - "My Lower East Side", undated (Box 9, Folder 569)
    - "Larry Stanton", undated (Box 9, Folder 570)
    - [moved to different location], undated (Box 9, Folder 571-579)
    - "Bold Statement", undated (Box 9, Folder 580)
    - "Mythical Landscapes", undated (Box 9, Folder 581)
    - NYQ, "Zines from a Mall", undated (Box 9, Folder 582)
    - No Apologies, Interview, undated (Box 9, Folder 583)
    - On the Next Wave, "Tim Miller's.", undated (Box 9, Folder 584)
    - Out: Mea Culpa, "Queer King", undated (Box 9, Folder 585)
    - Piece! Yoko Ono Story, undated (Box 9, Folder 586)
  - Subseries E: Poetry News
    - Cooper manuscript, undated (Box 9, Folder 587)
    - 1980-81, undated (Box 9, Folder 588)
    - Poet Survey, undated (Box 9, Folder 589)
    - "In with the Out Crowd", undated (Box 9, Folder 590)
    - "Pre-Christmas News", undated (Box 9, Folder 591)
    - "Ten New Books", undated (Box 9, Folder 592)
    - Poetry Project, Report from Amsterdam, undated (Box 9, Folder 593)
    - Rundy's Journal, "N.Y. versus L.A.", undated (Box 9, Folder 594)
    - Shake! Correspondence about interview with Keanu Reeves, undated (Box 9, Folder 595)
  - Subseries F: Spin
    - Review of Alice in Chains, undated (Box 9, Folder 596)
    - "Altared State", undated (Box 9, Folder 597)
    - Black Fag, undated (Box 9, Folder 598)
    - CD Rom article proposal, undated (Box 9, Folder 599)
    - Article on Cheap Trick, undated (Box 9, Folder 600)
    - Correspondence about Christian Bale article, undated (Box 9, Folder 601)
    - David Cross article, undated (Box 9, Folder 602)
    - Review of Dinosaur Jr, undated (Box 9, Folder 603)
    - Favorite Book, undated (Box 9, Folder 604)
    - "FSOL Review", undated (Box 9, Folder 605)
    - "The Future of Rebellion", undated (Box 9, Folder 606)
    - "Future Sound", undated (Box 9, Folder 607)
    - Garbage Interview, undated (Box 9, Folder 608)
    - "Goldie", undated (Box 9, Folder 609)
    - Review of Goldin, undated (Box 9, Folder 610)
    - "Grain of the Voice", undated (Box 9, Folder 610a)
    - "Haas on Fire", undated (Box 9, Folder 611)
    - Homeless HIV+ Kid article, undated (Box 9, Folder 612)
    - Interview with Hudson--draft, undated (Box 9, Folder 613)
    - "Husker Du", undated (Box 9, Folder 614)
    - "My Room Review", undated (Box 9, Folder 615)
    - "Junkie See, Junkie Do?", undated (Box 9, Folder 616)
    - "Larry Clark" article proposal, undated (Box 9, Folder 617)
    - "Courtney Love", undated (Box 9, Folder 618)
    - Malkmus Interview, undated (Box 9, Folder 619)
    - Interview with director/stars of Modern Primates, undated (Box 9, Folder 620)
    - Interview with Bob Mould, undated (Box 9, Folder 621)
    - No Safety review, undated (Box 9, Folder 622)
    - River Phoenix article, undated (Box 9, Folder 623)
    - "Printed Matter", undated (Box 9, Folder 624)
    - Rebellion, undated (Box 10, Folder 625)
    - Review of Lydon's Rotten, undated (Box 10, Folder 626)
    - Sketch Artist, undated (Box 10, Folder 627)
    - Review of Superchunk, undated (Box 10, Folder 628)
    - Taboo., undated (Box 10, Folder 629)
    - Too Cool for School, undated (Box 10, Folder 630)
    - Gus van Sant article, undated (Box 10, Folder 631)
    - Cooper on Weissman, undated (Box 10, Folder 632)
  - Subseries G: Village Voice
    - Review of Pretending to Say No, undated (Box 10, Folder 633)
    - Edge City, undated (Box 10, Folder 634)
    - Queercore, undated (Box 10, Folder 635)
    - Voice Literary Supplement, undated (Box 10, Folder 636)
    - Voice Literary Supplement "Just and Disgust", undated (Box 10, Folder 637)
    - No Mo' Pomo, undated (Box 10, Folder 638)
    - The Emergence of Gay Writing, undated (Box 10, Folder 639)
    - West Coast Art Review, Reviews of Brad Gooch by Cooper, undated (Box 10, Folder 640)
  - Subseries H: Other Published and Unpublished Articles
    - Review of Anywhere., undated (Box 10, Folder 641)
    - Bale interview, undated (Box 10, Folder 642)
    - Book Reviews, undated (Box 10, Folder 643)
    - Review of Kathe Burkhart, undated (Box 10, Folder 644)
    - Review of Vija Celmins, undated (Box 10, Folder 645)
    - Review of Alan Charlton, undated (Box 10, Folder 646)
    - Review of Cheap Trick, undated (Box 10, Folder 647)
    - Review of Joe Coleman, undated (Box 10, Folder 648)
    - Dancenoise, undated (Box 10, Folder 649)
    - Review of Dana Duff, undated (Box 10, Folder 650)
    - Review of Ecstacy, undated (Box 10, Folder 651)
    - Review of Epigraph, undated (Box 10, Folder 652)
    - Five Reasons to Read, undated (Box 10, Folder 653)
    - Review of Garnet Puet, undated (Box 10, Folder 654)
    - Gay Literature, undated (Box 10, Folder 655)
    - The Great Lost Same, undated (Box 10, Folder 656)
    - Review of Robbe Grillet, undated (Box 10, Folder 657)
    - Review of works by Harvey, undated (Box 10, Folder 658)
    - Review of Home Show, undated (Box 10, Folder 659)
    - How I Met., undated (Box 10, Folder 660)
    - Review of Peter Huttinger, undated (Box 10, Folder 661)
    - The Importance of Being ABBA, undated (Box 10, Folder 662)
    - Interview notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 663)
    - Interview notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 664)
    - Jazz/Pop Polls, undated (Box 10, Folder 665)
    - Review of Jim Isermann, undated (Box 10, Folder 666)
    - Jim Isermann interview Catalogue, Feature Gallery, New York City, undated (Box 10, Folder 667)
    - Review of Steven King's It, undated (Box 10, Folder 668)
    - Review of GB Jones, undated (Box 10, Folder 669)
    - Review of Mike Kelly, undated (Box 10, Folder 670)
    - L.A. Club Scene, undated (Box 10, Folder 671)
    - L.A. Poetry, undated (Box 10, Folder 672)
    - L.A. Poets, undated (Box 10, Folder 673)
    - Cooper on Miller, undated (Box 10, Folder 674)
    - Review of Need, undated (Box 10, Folder 675)
    - Review of Wessel O'Conner, undated (Box 10, Folder 676)
    - Interview Pieter on Man-Boy Love, undated (Box 10, Folder 677)
    - Article on Raymond Pettibon--Catalogue, Raymond Pettibon, Kunsthalle Basel, undated (Box 10, Folder 678)
    - Poetry Review, undated (Box 10, Folder 679)
    - Pornography, undated (Box 10, Folder 680)
    - Review of Carter Potter, undated (Box 10, Folder 681)
    - Rave Culture Article, undated (Box 10, Folder 682)
    - Charles Ray Interview--Catalogue, Charles Ray, Newport Harbor Art Museum, undated (Box 10, Folder 683)
    - Review of Remember Me, undated (Box 10, Folder 684)
    - Review of 'Representing Vietnam', undated (Box 10, Folder 685)
    - Review of James Schuyler, undated (Box 10, Folder 686)
    - Review of Andres Serrano, undated (Box 10, Folder 687)
    - Review of Sonic Youth's Sister--liner notes fro Geffen rerelease of Sister CD, undated (Box 10, Folder 688)
    - Review of Alan Turner, undated (Box 10, Folder 689)
    - Review of Julie Wachtel, undated (Box 10, Folder 690)
    - Review of Douglas Walker, undated (Box 10, Folder 691)
    - Review of Adolf Wolfli, undated (Box 10, Folder 692)
    - Review of David Wojnarowicz, undated (Box 10, Folder 693)
    - Review of B. Wurtz, undated (Box 10, Folder 694)
    - Review of Fidel Marquez, undated (Box 10, Folder 695)
    - Review of Duane Michals, undated (Box 10, Folder 696)
    - Review of John Miller, undated (Box 10, Folder 697)
    - John Miller--catalogue, John Miller, undated (Box 10, Folder 698)
    - Review of Donald Moffett, undated (Box 10, Folder 699)
    - Review of Robert Morris, undated (Box 10, Folder 700)
    - Review of Bob Mould, undated (Box 10, Folder 701)
    - Ryu Murakami article, undated (Box 10, Folder 702)
- Series IV: Biographical material and personal correspondence
  - Subseries A: Biographical material
    - Biographical, Biography, undated (Box 10, Folder 703)
    - Biographical, Biography on Cooper by Earl Jackson Jr, undated (Box 10, Folder 704)
    - Biographical, college material, undated (Box 10, Folder 705)
    - Biographical, College Registration 1975, undated (Box 10, Folder 706)
    - Biographical, headshot, undated (Box 10, Folder 707)
    - Biographical, Resume, undated (Box 10, Folder 708)
    - Cooper, Ann--Correspondence, undated (Box 10, Folder 709)
    - Cooper, Cindy--Correspondence, undated (Box 10, Folder 710)
    - Cooper, Clifford--correspondence, undated (Box 10, Folder 711)
    - Cooper, Clifford--manuscript, undated (Box 10, Folder 712)
    - Cooper, Courtney--Correspondence, undated (Box 10, Folder 713)
    - Diary 1976-1977, undated (Box 10, Folder 714)
    - Diary 1978-1981, undated (Box 10, Folder 715)
    - Diary Scrapbook, Prostitutes 1983, undated (Box 10, Folder 716)
    - Family Christmas Cards, undated (Box 10, Folder 717)
    - Family Photographs, undated (Box 10, Folder 718)
    - Juvenalia, "I'm Sorry I Bent Your Feathers", undated (Box 10, Folder 719)
    - Juvenalia, Press, undated (Box 10, Folder 720)
    - Juvenalia, unfinished memoir, undated (Box 10, Folder 721)
    - Lecture given at Langston Street San Francisco, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 722)
    - Lecture given at Outwrite conference, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 723)
    - Lecture given at "New Narrative" panel, Outwrite conference, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 724)
    - Feature presents: an Evening of New Ficton with Dennis Cooper and Casey McKinney, undated (Box 10, Folder 725)
    - The United States of Poetry, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 726)
    - Dennis Cooper featured author at Festival of Books, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 727)
    - press coverage of reading, Chicago, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 728)
    - New City reading, Dennis Cooper and Bobby Anderson, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 729)
    - Frances Stark presents an evening of reading. Los Angeles, undated (Box 10, Folder 730)
    - Beyond Baroque benefit, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 731)
    - Readings and conversations, Amy Gerstler and Dennis Cooper, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 732)
    - Dennis Cooper, Tim Dlugos reading tour, Philadelphia, Washington DC and Boston., undated (Box 10, Folder 733)
    - Works and Words, undated (Box 10, Folder 734)
    - Gay Poetry Night with Dennis Cooper, Robert Peters and David Trinidad, undated (Box 10, Folder 735)
    - A poetry reading at Clouds, Pasadena CA, undated (Box 10, Folder 736)
    - Dennis Cooper, Tim Dlugos, Alice Notley read their poems, undated (Box 10, Folder 737)
    - The L.A. Scene: Los Angeles Poets, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 738)
    - A Reading of Poetry and Prose, Edmund White and Dennis Cooper, undated (Box 10, Folder 739)
    - Poetry Downtown, a reading by Dennis Cooper and James Krusoe (Box 10, Folder 740)
    - Little Caesar Press spring titles book party, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 741)
    - Spoken Words, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 742)
    - Beyond Baroque reading: Dennis Cooper and Tim Dlugos, undated (Box 10, Folder 743)
    - Village Voice, comming attractions, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 744)
    - Dennis Cooper and Felice Picano, undated (Box 10, Folder 745)
    - Poetry at Midnight with Felice Picano and Dennis Cooper, undated (Box 10, Folder 746)
    - Dennis Cooper at The Ear Inn, undated (Box 10, Folder 747)
    - The Marriage of Heaven and Hell poetry origram, undated (Box 10, Folder 748)
    - Glad Fridays Visiting Lesbian and Gay Writers series, undated (Box 10, Folder 749)
    - Archives' events, Celebrating Lesbian and Gay culture., 1981 (Box 10, Folder 750)
    - Readings at the Ear Inn, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 751)
    - A Different Light, Gay Literature, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 752)
    - Intellectuals and Liars reading schedule, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 753)
    - New College Poetry readings, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 754)
    - From Our Heart's To Yours, a Men's Valentine's Poetry Reading, undated (Box 10, Folder 755)
    - A Poetry Reading at the Hyperion Theater, undated (Box 10, Folder 756)
    - Poetry Reading at Clesea Bookstore, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 757)
    - Cooper and Picano at The Glines, undated (Box 10, Folder 758)
    - Pasadena Community Arts Center Poetry Series, undated (Box 10, Folder 759)
    - Poetry at Clouds, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 760)
    - Intellectuals and Liars: Dennis Cooper and Michael Silverblatt, undated (Box 10, Folder 761)
    - The Hyperion Theatre The Poets Place, undated (Box 10, Folder 762)
    - South Bay Live, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 763)
    - Dennis Cooper reading at Intellectuals and Liars, undated (Box 10, Folder 764)
    - LA Library Poetry Reading, Wanda Coleman and Dennis Cooper, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 765)
    - Small Press Traffic Reading, undated (Box 10, Folder 766)
    - Beyond Baroque reading, undated (Box 10, Folder 767)
    - Beyond Baroque reading in Datebook, undated (Box 10, Folder 768)
    - Salon reading, undated (Box 10, Folder 769)
    - Original Language Poetry Series, undated (Box 10, Folder 770)
    - Poetry for Punks, undated (Box 10, Folder 771)
    - Gay Sunshine Benefit Poetry Reading, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 772)
    - Rimbaud's Birthday, undated (Box 10, Folder 773)
    - Reading by Student Poets, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 774)
    - Poets, undated (Box 10, Folder 775)
    - Pasadena Community Arts Center Poetry Series, undated (Box 10, Folder 776)
    - The Hyperion Theatre, the Poets Place, undated (Box 10, Folder 777)
    - Evening of Poetry with Dennis Cooper, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 778)
    - Dennis Cooper Reads, undated (Box 10, Folder 779)
    - Poetry Benefit for the Company Theater, undated (Box 10, Folder 780)
    - Reading at Matthew Marks Gallery, Dennis Cooper and Kevin Killian, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 781)
    - Dennis Cooper reading at Bop Shop, undated (Box 10, Folder 782)
    - Examples Cool and Lonely, undated (Box 10, Folder 783)
    - Farm Boys reading, undated (Box 10, Folder 784)
    - PEN American Center and Center for Lesbian and Gay Studies present an Evening of Gay Men's Literature, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 785)
    - Reading pick of the Week, undated (Box 10, Folder 786)
    - Writer Riot, undated (Box 10, Folder 787)